George M. Gray Museum Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- 35mm Slide Collection, Series I
  - Specimens., 003323
    - Platynereis dumerilii. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Aug 1965., 003276
    - Platynereis dumerilii. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Aug 1965., 003277
    - Platynereis dumerilii. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Aug 1965., 003278
    - Podarke obscura. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 17 Jul 1965., 003279
    - Podarke obscura. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 17 Jul 1965., 003280
    - Polchorus caudatus. 35mm Slide Menemsha, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 22 Nov 1965., 003123
    - Polycera dubia. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Canal, Sandwich, MA. 01 Sep 1963., 003200
    - Polycera dubia. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003201
    - Polycera dubia. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003202
    - Polymastia robusta. 35mm Slide.off Chatham, MA. 41D 41.9'N, 69D 46.8' W. 20 Oct 1964., 003081
    - Polymastia robusta. 35mm Slide.off Chatham, MA. 41D 41.9'N, 69D 46.8' W. 20 Oct 1964., 003082
    - Potamilla reniformis. 35mm Slide off Emerson's, Nonamesset Island, MA. 14 Sep 1965., 003281
    - Potamilla reniformis. 35mm Slide off Nashawena Island, Buzzards Bay, MA. 17 Aug 1965., 003282
    - Potamilla reniformis. 35mm Slide off Nashawena Island, Buzzards Bay, MA. 17 Aug 1965., 003283
    - Pycnaphyes frequens. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 37' 20"N, 70D 45' 05"W. 29 Jul 1966., 003133
    - Sabellaria vulgaris. 35mm Slide off Emerson's, Nonamesset Island, MA. 14 Sep 1965., 003284
    - Sabellaria vulgaris. 35mm Slide off Emerson's, Nonamesset Island, MA. 14 Sep 1965., 003285
    - Scalibregma inflatum. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 07 Jun 1966., 003286
    - Scyllaea pelagica. 35mm Slide Woods Hole, MA. Jan 1963., 003203
    - Semibalanus balanoides. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 05 Nov 1964., 003304
    - Solemya velum. 35mm Slide Tashmoo Pond, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 08 May 1966., 003217
    - Spio setosa. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 07 Jun 1966., 003287
    - Spio setosa. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 07 Jun 1966., 003288
    - Spirorbis borealis. 35mm Slide Toby Island, Monument Beach, MA. Aug 1965., 003289
    - Stenothoe minuta. 35mm Slide Quick's Hole, MA. 06 Jan 1964., 003311
    - Sternapsis scutata. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003290
    - Sternapsis scutata. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003291
    - Sternapsis scutata. 35mm Slide SE of Gay Head, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 28 Mar 1967., 003292
    - Sthenelais boa. 35mm Slide Nobska Point, Woods Hole, MA> 23 Jun 1965., 003293
    - Stiliger fuscatus. 35mm Slide Aquaculture Lab, Dennis, MA. 13 Jan 1966., 003204
    - Stiliger fuscatus. 35mm Slide Aquaculture Lab, Dennis, MA. 13 Jan 1966., 003205
    - Stomatopoda. 35mm Slide Sep 1965., 003305
    - Stylochus zebra. 35mm Slide Waquoit Bay, MA. 26 Aug 1965., 003124
    - Stylochus zebra. 35mm Slide Waquoit Bay, MA. 26 Aug 1965., 003125
    - Stylochus zebra. 35mm Slide Waquoit Bay, MA. 26 Aug 1965., 003126
    - Syllis cornuta. 35mm Slide off Cuttyhunk Island, MA. 30 Jun 1966., 003294
    - Sympleustes glaber. 35mm Slide Quick's Hole, MA. 25 Mar 1964., 003312
    - Tergipes tergipes. 35mm Slide Menemsha Bight, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 08 Nov 1965., 003206
    - Tubularia couthouyi. 35mm Slide Fisheries Jetty, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Nov 1964., 003097
    - Tubularia couthouyi. 35mm Slide Fisheries Jetty, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Nov 1964., 003098
    - Tubularia couthouyi. 35mm Slide MBL Sea Table. 31 Jan 1966., 003099
    - Tubularia crocea. 35mm Slide Woods Hole, MA. Dec 1962, 003100
    - Zirfaea crispata. 35mm Slide Apr 1967., 003218
- Original Labels, Series II
  - Gray Museum Labels. These are archived Gray Museum labels removed from specimens., 1960-1994; 001959
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 1134, 1960-1994; 001960
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 475., 1960-1994; 001961
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3940., 1960-1994; 001962
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3847., 1960-1994; 001963
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4255., 1960-1994; 001964
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 648., 1960-1994; 001965
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 220., 1960-1994; 001966
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4707., 1960-1994; 001967
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4320., 1960-1994; 001968
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 219., 1960-1994; 001969
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 636., 1960-1994; 001970
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7585., 1960-1994; 001971
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 447., 1960-1994; 001972
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 993., 1960-1994; 001973
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4642., 1960-1994; 001974
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3986., 1960-1994; 001975
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4689., 1960-1994; 001976
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4552., 1960-1994; 001977
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7034., 1960-1994; 001978
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4305., 1960-1994; 001979
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 595., 1960-1994; 001980
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3794., 1960-1994; 001981
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 295., 1960-1994; 001984
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 484., 1960-1994; 001985
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3988., 1960-1994; 001986
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 451., 1960-1994; 001987
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3769., 1960-1994; 001988
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 452., 1960-1994; 001989
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3987., 1960-1994; 001990
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 348., 1960-1994; 001991
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 775., 1960-1994; 001992
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 347., 1960-1994; 001993
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2894., 1960-1994; 001994
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4134., 1960-1994; 001995
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7037., 1960-1994; 001996
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7039., 1960-1994; 001997
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7588., 1960-1994; 001998
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3072., 1960-1994; 001999
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2236., 1960-1994; 002000
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 433., 1960-1994; 002001
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4856., 1960-1994; 002002
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 6614., 1960-1994; 002003
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 6615., 1960-1994; 002004
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 6616., 1960-1994; 002005
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 6617., 1960-1994; 002006
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 6618., 1960-1994; 002007
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2922., 1960-1994; 002008
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3573., 1960-1994; 002009
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 585., 1960-1994; 002010
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7037., 1960-1994; 002011
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 349., 1960-1994; 002012
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2333., 1960-1994; 002013
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 752., 1960-1994; 002014
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3839., 1960-1994; 002015
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4285., 1960-1994; 002018
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 327., 1960-1994; 002019
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 631., 1960-1994; 002020
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 2334., 1960-1994; 002671
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4502., 1960-1994; 002672
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 632., 1960-1994; 002673
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7584., 1960-1994; 002674
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3944., 1960-1994; 002675
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 246., 1960-1994; 002676
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original determination label. See attached objects., 1960-1994; 002677
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3800., 1960-1994; 002678
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7586., 1960-1994; 002679
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 216., 1960-1994; 002680
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for YPM No's. 63743-63747. GM No. 7050 is not the correct number according to the GM catalog sheets. The correct GM number is unknown., 1960-1994; 002683
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4739., 1960-1994; 002684
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4075., 1960-1994; 002685
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4164., 1960-1994; 002686
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3404., 1960-1994; 002687
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7587., 1960-1994; 002688
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 915., 1960-1994; 002689
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3388., 1960-1994; 002690
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3385., 1960-1994; 002691
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3380., 1960-1994; 002692
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3387. Specimen has been lost., 1960-1994; 002697
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 2745., 1960-1994; 002698
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3063., 1960-1994; 002699
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3941., 1960-1994; 002700
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4462., 1960-1994; 002701
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 649., 1960-1994; 002702
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 483., 1960-1994; 002703
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 740., 1960-1994; 002704
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7581., 1960-1994; 002705
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3963., 1960-1994; 002706
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 745., 1960-1994; 002710
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4052., 1960-1994; 002711
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4851., 1960-1994; 002712
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3915., 1960-1994; 002713
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 645., 1960-1994; 002714
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4321., 1960-1994; 002715
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4395., 1960-1994; 002717
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4380., 1960-1994; 002719
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7040., 1960-1994; 002720
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 448., 1960-1994; 002721
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 486., 1960-1994; 002722
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 538., 1960-1994; 002723
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7042., 1960-1994; 002724
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 550., 1960-1994; 002725
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3988., 1960-1994; 002726
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4192., 1960-1994; 002727
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7580., 1960-1994; 002728
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4384., 1960-1994; 002729
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3829., 1960-1994; 002730
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4155., 1960-1994; 002731
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 1400., 1960-1994; 002732
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3968., 1960-1994; 002733
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 548., 1960-1994; 002734
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 644., 1960-1994; 002735
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 450., 1960-1994; 002736
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 1168., 1960-1994; 002737
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3991., 1960-1994; 002738
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4227., 1960-1994; 002739
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 291., 1960-1994; 002740
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4319., 1960-1994; 002741
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7576., 1960-1994; 002742
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4047., 1960-1994; 002743
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4751., 1960-1994; 002744
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3572., 1960-1994; 002745
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 420., 1960-1994; 002746
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3423., 1960-1994; 002747
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7254., 1960-1994; 002748
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label. See Attachments., 1960-1994; 002749
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7286., 1960-1994; 002750
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 6691., 1960-1994; 002751
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7015., 1960-1994; 002752
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7253., 1960-1994; 002753
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7419., 1960-1994; 002754
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4551., 1960-1994; 002755
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 335., 1960-1994; 002756
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 2777., 1960-1994; 002761
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3942., 1960-1994; 002762
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3943., 1960-1994; 002763
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 4344., 1960-1994; 002764
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7255., 1960-1994; 002770
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7256., 1960-1994; 002771
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 7236., 1960-1994; 002772
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for YPM No. 33826 (GM No. 6400)., 1960-1994; 002775
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 2300., 1960-1994; 002776
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for YPM No. 69333 - 69339. (No GM numbers), 1960-1994; 002777
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 2349., 1960-1994; 002778
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 2350., 1960-1994; 002779
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 537., 1960-1994; 002781
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 1129., 1960-1994; 002782
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM No. 3957., 1960-1994; 002783
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for YPM No. 70175 - 70176. (No GM numbers)., 1960-1994; 002784
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2248., 1960-1994; 002789
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2250., 1960-1994; 002790
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7017., 1960-1994; 002800
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7010. (YPM No's 70408-70426)., 1960-1994; 002805
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 236., 1960-1994; 002807
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2134., 1960-1994; 002808
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3636., 1960-1994; 002809
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 920., 1960-1994; 002820
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3401., 1960-1994; 002822
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 471., 1960-1994; 002823
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7420., 1960-1994; 002824
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3816., 1960-1994; 002825
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3831., 1960-1994; 002826
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2879., 1960-1994; 002827
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2936., 1960-1994; 002828
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3815., 1960-1994; 002829
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3038., 1960-1994; 002830
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3418., 1960-1994; 002831
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3021., 1960-1994; 002832
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2822., 1960-1994; 002833
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3008., 1960-1994; 002834
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3029., 1960-1994; 002835
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3425., 1960-1994; 002836
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2882., 1960-1994; 002837
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3937., 1960-1994; 002838
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3069., 1960-1994; 003715
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2861., 1960-1994; 003716
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3793., 1960-1994; 003717
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3760., 1960-1994; 003718
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3328., 1960-1994; 003719
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3415., 1960-1994; 003720
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3410., 1960-1994; 003721
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3234., 1960-1994; 003722
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4596., 1960-1994; 003723
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3776., 1960-1994; 003724
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4855., 1960-1994; 003725
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2852., 1960-1994; 003726
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3442., 1960-1994; 003727
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 252., 1960-1994; 005000
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 269., 1960-1994; 005001
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7578., 1960-1994; 005002
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7589., 1960-1994; 005003
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7590., 1960-1994; 005004
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 272., 1960-1994; 005662
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 306., 1960-1994; 005663
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 600., 1960-1994; 005683
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 696., 1960-1994; 005684
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 744., 1960-1994; 005685
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 674., 1960-1994; 005686
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7046., 1960-1994; 005687
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7044., 1960-1994; 005688
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7595., 1960-1994; 005693
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7594., 1960-1994; 005694
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7041., 1960-1994; 005695
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2325., 1960-1994; 005696
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 789., 1960-1994; 005697
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3497., 1960-1994; 005701
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4708., 1960-1994; 005702
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 976., 1960-1994; 005703
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4033., 1960-1994; 005704
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3694., 1960-1994; 005705
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 1671., 1960-1994; 005706
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7192., 1960-1994; 005707
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3319., 1960-1994; 005708
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4014., 1960-1994; 005709
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4413., 1960-1994; 005733
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4439., 1960-1994; 005734
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4145., 1960-1994; 005735
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4606., 1960-1994; 005736
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7184., 1960-1994; 005737
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7188., 1960-1994; 005738
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 1147., 1960-1994; 005921
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 1327., 1960-1994; 005922
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 1265., 1960-1994; 005924
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 7009., 1960-1994; 005925
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 449., 1960-1994; 005927
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 630., 1960-1994; 005929
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 422., 1960-1994; 005933
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4512., 1960-1994; 005934
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 2866., 1960-1994; 005935
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 4890, 1960-1994; 005936
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM No. 3246., 1960-1994; 005937
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for YPM No. 33794., 1960-1994; 005938
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 421., 1960-1994; 006432
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 7377., 1960-1994; 006433
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 4473., 1960-1994; 006434
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 2970., 1960-1994; 006435
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 642., 1960-1994; 006436
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 929., 1960-1994; 006437
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7386., 1960-1994; 006438
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7384., 1960-1994; 006439
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 2775., 1960-1994; 006440
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 987., 1960-1994; 006441
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7422., 1960-1994; 006442
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 1737., 1960-1994; 006443
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 3608., 1960-1994; 006444
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 660., 1960-1994; 006445
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 2323., 1960-1994; 006446
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 667., 1960-1994; 006447
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 2335., 1960-1994; 006448
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 3717., 1960-1994; 006449
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 3402., 1960-1994; 006450
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7421., 1960-1994; 006451
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 3413., 1960-1994; 006452
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7591., 1960-1994; 006453
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 1212., 1960-1994; 006454
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7593., 1960-1994; 006455
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7390., 1960-1994; 006456
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 741., 1960-1994; 006457